

### **ABOUT ME**

An enthusiastic and self-motivated Software Engineer with an extensive experience more than 5 years in designing, developing and testing software.

Strong background in process-oriented software development. Capable of working in a team environment or working independently. I am continually seeking new challenges and a desire to expand knowledge and experience.

#### **SKILLS & EXPERTISE**

- · Web Development
- Mobile Development
- · Basic Networking

## **ACADEMIC BACKGROUND**

## STT Duta Bangsa

Bachelor's Degree in Information Technology | 2021

- Study program : Computer Network & Web Programming
- GPA 3.57

## SMKN 1 Lemahsugih

Senior High School | 2015

- Have internship experience at Telkom University
- Joined web development competition activities

# AGIS R HERDIANA

WEB & MOBILE DEVELOPER

### **PREVIOUS POSITIONS**

#### Mobile Developer

KAI Services | 2022 - Present

- Build Android and iOS app using the same codebase
- Reduce the time of development and release apps faster as a consequence
- Create a complex, custom UI with ease

#### Full Stack (Backend, Frontend & Mobile Developer)

Total Logistics | 2018 - 2022

- Build and develop applications for internal companies, client or vendor
- · Development in logistics and sales.

## HRIS Developer

Axiopro | 2017 - 2018

- Focus for developing Human Resource Information System
- Work with HR, finance and IT to maintain and improve the HRIS, including configuration, end-user access, security, and system efficiency
- Supports critical system maintenance and operational tasks within the HRIS

## **REACH ME AT:**

- Email: agis.rahma.herdiana@gmail.com
- Portfolio: https://agisrh.github.io



